Hiu Wing, Lam

Recent university graduate with computer science major. Proficient in a range of modern technologies including Microsoft Office software, HTML, CSS, PHP, MySQL and Java application. Can work well both independently and in a team. Experience working in the service industry with the understanding of customer service. Hard-working, very patient, proactive individual with strong problem-solving and the ability to learn new concepts fast.

Education

BS in Computer Science

08/2018 - 12/2020

Brooklyn College. Brooklyn, NY

GPA: 3.35 / 4.00

Relevant Coursework:

 Design and Implementation Web Application, Database Systems, Computer Architecture, Data Structure, Operation Systems, Analysis of Algorithms in Computer Science, Discrete Structure in Computer Science

Honors & Awards: Dean's List (2020)

AAS in Computer Information System

03/2017 - 06/2018

Kingsborough Community College. Brooklyn, NY

GPA: 3.41 / 4.00

Relevant Coursework:

 Object-Oriented Programming, Network Server Administration, Advance Personal Computer Techniques for Business, Advance Programming Techniques, Web Page Development, Java for Programmers

Extracurricular Activities

SBUHacks 2020

September 25-26, 2020

Description:

 A 24 hour hackathon where students are challenged to further what they know by doing projects on what they are passionate about.

My Project: Gaia - A mobile app

• This app will help individuals calculating their carbon footprint consumption, offers a personalized recommendation on the "quick wins" action that they can do based on their inputs, and offer a donate feature for them that will be used to fund environmental and conservation acts. With this, users will be fully aware of their significant involvement in this issue and have the chance to act straight away to offset the negative externalities that they have caused.

Personal Information

■ Address:

531, 51st Street, Brooklyn,

NY 11220

■ Phone:

646-853-6534

■ E-mail:

hilda11224@gmail.com

■ Personal Website:

https://hiuwing0107.github.io/PersonalWebsitePortfolio/

■ GitHub:

https://github.com/hiuwing0107?t ab=repositories

Technical Skills

Java: 4 years

HTML/CSS: 4 years

• PHP: 1 year

JavaScript: 2 years

MySQL Database: 1 year

• Figma: 2 years

Adobe Photoshop: 2 years

• Adobe Premiere: 2 years

Adobe After Effects: 1 year

Skills in Mircosoft Office: 4 years

<u>Languages</u>

- English
- Chinese (Cantonese)
- Chinese (Mandarin)

Work Experiences

Customer Receptionist

08/2018 - Present

Running Kids.Inc, Kids Indoor Playground. Brooklyn, NY

Key Qualifications & Responsibilities:

- Greeting and welcoming guests and providing them with a positive first impression of the company
- · Handling incoming calls and take the messages from customers
- · Directing customers and deal with their complaints or problems
- Pick up the order and collect customer's payments through the POS system
- · Schedule and confirm the party reservation

Restaurant Server

01/2016 - 02/2017

Formosa Cuisine, Asian and Vegetarian Restaurant. Poughkeepsie, NY Key Qualifications & Responsibilities

- Greet and escort customers to their tables
- Present menu and provide detailed information when asked
- · Arrange table settings and maintain a tidy dining area
- · Handling incoming calls and take the delivery orders
- · Pick up the order and collect customer's payments through the POS system
- · Deliver food and drinks to the customers' tables

Interests

- Designing Websites
- Video Editing
- Traveling
- Listening to Music